<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Subscribe to furniture? on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Subscribe to furniture? on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gathering</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</guid>
      <description>Hemmlis finds most of our furniture through second-hand sources. Some we collect from individuals on second hand platforms online, while other furniture reaches us through partners like Emmaus Fredriksdal. For some collections we purchase specific pieces of furniture from second hand stores or flea markets.
We also receive donations from individuals, contacting us directly through our facebook page or email address. We try to collect furniture in the immediate area around Lund, to decrease environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</guid>
      <description>Our first task is always to sanitize incoming furniture with industry proven cleaning methods such as vacuuming, soap washing and steam washing, using environmental friendly products. This is particularly essential for textile furniture, mattresses and beds which we also treat with eco friendly methods. Subsequently we repair and upcycle the furniture when needed, by eg. repainting or repolishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The collections</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:28:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</guid>
      <description>Our collections consist of 5-6 different pieces of furniture, meshed together to create a uniform design concept. At times we even invite our guest designers to the workshop to create exciting eclectic (mixed) design concepts ranging from vintage to modern or even nordic design and rokoko. Our collections are custom made for a student room of about 15-20 square meters and always delivered together as as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your order</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</guid>
      <description>Our minimum leasing subscriptions starts at one semester (about five months) to a cost of 499:- a month. Our longer standard subscription has a minimum of 10 months and is then changed to ongoing subscription at 399:- a month.
All furniture will be delivered to your home address, and we will provide repairs if the need should arise, as well as pickup of the collection at the end of the term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The circle is complete</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</guid>
      <description>Furniture that have been out will be reintroduced into our circular system where it’s sanitized anew, and refreshed in time for the next subscriber. This way we create an alternative model for furniture consupmtion which we believe will reduce furniture waste and the environmental impact.
To succeed in this, it is crucial for us that our furniture be used responsibly. We put all out faith in that you, our customers help us out in this so that we can continue to offer you neat collections of furniture in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retake</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of service for Hemmlis (Sin Pantal EF)</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/contract/</guid>
      <description>§1. Lease term  The rentee commits to renting the furniture for the duration specified while ordering. After the duration specified has expired the service is renewed monthly until the rentee or the renter terminates the agreement.  §2. Price  The price of the furniture is presented in the documentation received after booking the furniture. Included in the price are; delivery, collection and reparations or exchange of damaged furniture during the lease term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2003</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 16:35:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2003/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:33:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2006/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2005</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:32:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2005/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2004</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:27:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2004/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2002</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:14:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2002/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2001</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2001/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1005</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:07:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1005/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1004</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:05:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1004/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1003</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 19:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1003/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1002</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 17:29:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1002/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1001</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 16:30:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1001/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kobe</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 16:10:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</guid>
      <description>Sleeping on the floor might work for some, but Kobe from Belgium appreciated the fact having a bed the same day he arrived. He was also one of the first patrons to try out Hemmlis first collections from the fall of 2017 to the summer of 2018. We caught up with him as he was leaving Lund during his pick-up.
“First of all it was practical and such a relief not having to sleep on the floor when I arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something went wrong!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</guid>
      <description>Please try again or contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your home will soon be a home!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</guid>
      <description>An order confirmation has been sent to your email.
You will receive a text message within 24 hours confirming your delivery date. For support please contact us on order@hemmlis.se or +46 (0)46 276 90 06.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I exchange a piece of furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-substitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-substitution/</guid>
      <description>We offer the collections as they are. If you would like to replace a piece of furniture you can contact us and we will do our best to fulfill your request, however we can not guarantee the possibility of replacing furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are the furniture delivered?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Delivery to your sidewalk is included in your subscription. We deliver evenings and weekends. Your delivery date will be confirmed by text message (or email) within 24 hours of your order.
Help carrying the furniture into your apartment is available for small one time fee of 499 kr (VAT included).
Our goal is to deliver the furniture the same day that you get access to your room. However, if there are many who are wishing to have their furniture delivered the same day, we reserve ourselves for potential delays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I pay?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-payment/</guid>
      <description>We use PayPal to invoice you by e-mail. Your invoice is sent out at the beginning of your subscription on a per-semester basis. You can opt to pay everything at once or split up at your own discretion during your subscription period. After your binding period is up you will be invoiced monthly. Note that transaction fees may apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long is the subscription period?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-length/</guid>
      <description>We offer a subscription with a minimum subscription period (ie. &amp;ldquo;binding period&amp;rdquo;) of 5 months, perfect for one semester! Our standard subscription, which is slightly cheaper, requires at least a 10 month subscription.
After your binding period is up your subscription continues on a monthly basis until you want to end or upgrade it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens if something breaks?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-breakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-breakage/</guid>
      <description>If a piece of furniture breaks we take care of repairs or deliver a replacement piece. If the damage is due to normal usage (i.e &amp;ldquo;wear-and-tear&amp;rdquo;) this will not cost you anything. Further details are available in the documentation provided with the furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when I want to end my subscription?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-ending/</guid>
      <description>When you are done with your furniture simply contact us and we will come and collect the furniture at an agreed upon date. This is included in your subscription!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is included?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-included/</guid>
      <description>Included in the price for both subscriptions is a to-your-door-delivery, pick up of your furniture and a collection of the following furniture types:
 One 90 cm wide bed with a mattress pad One bookshelf One chair One table (desk or small kitchen table depending on collection) One nightstand One armchair  You can opt for a wider bed (&amp;ldquo;king size&amp;rdquo;, 120 cm) at a slightly increased cost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who can subscribe to the service?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-who/</guid>
      <description>Anyone can subscribe to our collections! However, they are a perfect fit for a basic student room (of about 15 to 20 square meters).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>