<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lease furniture? on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lease furniture? on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gathering</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</guid>
      <description>Hemmlis finds all our furniture through second hand sources. Some we collect from individuals on second hand platforms online, while other furniture reaches us through partners like Emmaus Lund. For some collections we purchase specific pieces of furniture from second hand stores or flea markets.
We also receive donations from individuals, contacting us directly through our facebook page or email address. We try to collect furniture in the immediate area around Lund, to decrease environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</guid>
      <description>Our first task is always to sanitize incoming furniture with industry proven cleaning methods such as vacuuming, soap washing and steam washing, using environmental friendly products. This is particularly essential for textile furniture, mattresses and beds which we also treat with eco friendly methods. Subsequently we repair and upcycle the furniture when needed, by eg. repainting or repolishing.
Occasionally we reconstruct furniture or change specific parts completely to add function or aesthetically pleasing pieces to our furniture collections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The collections</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:28:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</guid>
      <description>Our collections consist of 5-6 different pieces of furniture, meshed together to create a uniform design concept. At times we even invite our guest designers to the workshop to create exciting eclectic (mixed) design concepts ranging from vintage to modern or even nordic design and rokoko. Our collections are custom made for a student room of about 15-20 square meters and always leased as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your order</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</guid>
      <description>Our minimum leasing subscriptions starts at one semester (about five months) to a cost of 499:- a month.
All furniture will be delivered to your home address, and we will provide repairs if the need should arise, as well as pickup of the collection at the end of the term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The circle is complete</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</guid>
      <description>Furniture that have been leased will be reintroduced into our circular system where it’s sanitized anew, and refeshed in order to be leased again. This way we create an alternative model for furniture consumtion which we believe will reduce the wastage of furniture and the following negative impact it has on the environment.
To succeed in this, it is crucial for us that our furniture be used responsibly. We put all out faith in that you, our custimers help us out in this so that we can continue to offer you neat collections of furniture in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retake</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something went wrong!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</guid>
      <description>Please try again or contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your home will soon be a home!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</guid>
      <description>We will contact you within 24 hours to confirm your order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 13:31:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/004/</guid>
      <description>A modern purple collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 13:31:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/005/</guid>
      <description>A fresh 50&amp;rsquo;s style collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 13:31:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/006/</guid>
      <description>A cosy room with a classic vintage feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:54:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/001/</guid>
      <description>A mix of old and new, this room has a lot of contrast and color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:54:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/002/</guid>
      <description>A fresh style which combines clean modern lines with a touch of vintage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:54:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/003/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by nature, this room features custom made 3D printed lights. The room is designed by Oskar Olsson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I exchange a piece of furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-substitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-substitution/</guid>
      <description>We offer the collections as they are. If you would like to replace a piece of furniture you can contact us and we can check if we have something available. We can not guarantee the possibility of replacing furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are the furniture delivered?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-delivery/</guid>
      <description>We deliver to your doorstep at a time that we both agree to. Help carrying it into your apartment is available for small one time fee. Our goal is to deliver the furniture the same day that you get access to your room. However, if there are many who are wishing to have their furniture delivered the same day, delays might incur!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I pay?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-payment/</guid>
      <description>Invoices are sent out monthly to your e-mail address and on the invoices all information you need to pay are written. If you should wish we can make one large invoice at the start of the semester so that you only need to do one payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long is the lease period?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-length/</guid>
      <description>The lease period is at least one semester, during the spring semester that is until the middle/end of June (depending on program etc.) When you wish to return your furniture just tell us and we will book a date for collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens if something breaks?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-breakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-breakage/</guid>
      <description>If a piece of furniture breaks we come out and repair/replace it. If the damage is due to normal usage this will not cost you anything. See the lease contract for further details about this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when my lease is up?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-ending/</guid>
      <description>We collect the furniture at the end of the lease period at a date agreed between us and you. We carry the furniture from your apartment without further costs, provided we get access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is included?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-included/</guid>
      <description>Our collections consists of 5-6 different pieces of furniture, meshed together to create a uniform design concept suitable for a complete student room around 15-20 square meters. All furniture will be leased together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who can lease the furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-who/</guid>
      <description>We are mainly targeting students with our collections which means adjusting our collections to the limited living area of 15-20 square meters. However, we want everybody to have the opportunity to try out our collections and would be happy to receive other requests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>