<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lease furniture? on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lease furniture? on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gathering</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</guid>
      <description>Hemmlis finds most of our furniture through second-hand sources. Some we collect from individuals on second hand platforms online, while other furniture reaches us through partners like Emmaus Fredriksdal. For some collections we purchase specific pieces of furniture from second hand stores or flea markets.
We also receive donations from individuals, contacting us directly through our facebook page or email address. We try to collect furniture in the immediate area around Lund, to decrease environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</guid>
      <description>Our first task is always to sanitize incoming furniture with industry proven cleaning methods such as vacuuming, soap washing and steam washing, using environmental friendly products. This is particularly essential for textile furniture, mattresses and beds which we also treat with eco friendly methods. Subsequently we repair and upcycle the furniture when needed, by eg. repainting or repolishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The collections</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:28:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</guid>
      <description>Our collections consist of 5-6 different pieces of furniture, meshed together to create a uniform design concept. At times we even invite our guest designers to the workshop to create exciting eclectic (mixed) design concepts ranging from vintage to modern or even nordic design and rokoko. Our collections are custom made for a student room of about 15-20 square meters and always leased as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your order</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</guid>
      <description>Our minimum leasing subscriptions starts at one semester (about five months) to a cost of 499:- a month. Our longer standard subscription has a minimum of 10 months and is then changed to ongoing subscription at 399:- a month.
All furniture will be delivered to your home address, and we will provide repairs if the need should arise, as well as pickup of the collection at the end of the term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The circle is complete</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</guid>
      <description>Furniture that have been out will be reintroduced into our circular system where it’s sanitized anew, and refeshed in order to be leased again for another subscriber. This way we create an alternative model for furniture consupmtion which we believe will reduce furniture waste and the environmental impact.
To succeed in this, it is crucial for us that our furniture be used responsibly. We put all out faith in that you, our customers help us out in this so that we can continue to offer you neat collections of furniture in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retake</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:33:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2006/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2005</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:32:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2005/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2004</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:27:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2004/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2002</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:14:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2002/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 2001</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-2001/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1005</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:07:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1005/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1004</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:05:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1004/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1003</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 19:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1003/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1002</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 17:29:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1002/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kollektion 1001</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 16:30:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/collections/kollektion-1001/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kobe</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 16:10:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</guid>
      <description>Sleeping on the floor might work for some, but Kobe from Belgium appreciated the fact having a bed the same day he arrived. He was also one of the first patrons to try out Hemmlis first collections from the fall of 2017 to the summer of 2018. We caught up with him as he was leaving Lund during his pick-up.
“First of all it was practical and such a relief not having to sleep on the floor when I arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something went wrong!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/error/</guid>
      <description>Please try again or contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your home will soon be a home!</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:36:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/form/success/</guid>
      <description>We will contact you within 24 hours to confirm your order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I exchange a piece of furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-substitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-substitution/</guid>
      <description>We offer the collections as they are. If you would like to replace a piece of furniture you can contact us and we can check if we have something available. We can not guarantee the possibility of replacing furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are the furniture delivered?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-delivery/</guid>
      <description>We deliver to your doorstep at a time that we both agree to. Help carrying it into your apartment is available for small one time fee of 399 kr (VAT included). Your furniture pickup is included in the subscription! Our goal is to deliver the furniture the same day that you get access to your room. However, if there are many who are wishing to have their furniture delivered the same day, we reserve ourselves for potential delays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I pay?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-payment/</guid>
      <description>Invoices are sent out according to your subscription payment-plan (per month/quarter/whole sum directly) to your chosen e-mail address and on the invoices all information you need to pay are stated. Transactions can be made to directly to our bank or PayPal account. If you choose to pay through PayPal we will send you invoices where you can pay with you international bank card (observe that transaction fees might incur for currency exchanges).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long is the lease period?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-length/</guid>
      <description>The minimum subscription period we have is at least one semester (five (5) months). From a semester perspective, this would be until the middle/end of June (spring semester) and the middle of January (fall semester). Our other subscription period is for 10 months but is therefore abit cheaper! Delivery to your door and pickup is included in both subscription plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens if something breaks?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-breakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-breakage/</guid>
      <description>If a piece of furniture breaks we come out and repair/replace it. If the damage is due to normal usage (i.e &amp;ldquo;wear-and-tear&amp;rdquo;) this will not cost you anything. See your lease contract for further details about this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when my lease is up?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-ending/</guid>
      <description>We collect the furniture at the end of the lease period at a date agreed between us and you. We carry the furniture from your apartment without further costs, provided we have access to them. Pickup of your furniture is included in your subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is included?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-included/</guid>
      <description>Included in the price for both subscriptions is a to-your-door-delivery, pick up of your furniture and a collection of the following furniture types:
 One 90 cm wide bed with a fitted bed mattress One bookshelf One chair One table (desk or small kitchen table depending on collection) One nightstand One armchair  You can add extra services if you wish such as a wider bed (120 cm) or indoor delivery for an extra fee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who can lease the furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/faq/faq-who/</guid>
      <description>We are mainly targeting students with our collections which means adjusting our collections to the limited living area of 15-20 square meters. However, we want everybody to have the opportunity to try out our collections and would of course be happy to receive other requests. We are constantly curious about who else that could be interested in joining our circular economy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>