<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stories on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:53:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ward &amp; Quinten</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/ward-quinten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:53:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/ward-quinten/</guid>
      <description>This years (2018) autumn batch of international students were a bit fewer (around 1 000 less), so we didn’t really know what flow to expect to our booth at Lund Information Fair, hosted by International Desk at the university. Still numbering quite the few however, the day was amazing for us with lots of opportunities to talk to would-be customers and also getting feedback on the student needs in Lund and also all the positive energy and feedback on our service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna &amp; Evan</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/anna-evan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 16:46:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/anna-evan/</guid>
      <description>The only thing certain in student life is turbulence, something our Norwegian patron Anna Parnefält Störksen found already upon entering Swedish air space.
“Our plane was delayed as you remember, but you guys were really understanding and solved my delivery without fuss.”
Because the only way to counter balance instability - whether airbound or in life in general - is flexibility. That’s why Hemmlis doesn&amp;rsquo;t just rent out furniture, we provide the service of feeling at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kobe</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 16:10:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/stories/kobe/</guid>
      <description>Sleeping on the floor might work for some, but Kobe from Belgium appreciated the fact having a bed the same day he arrived. He was also one of the first patrons to try out Hemmlis first collections from the fall of 2017 to the summer of 2018. We caught up with him as he was leaving Lund during his pick-up.
“First of all it was practical and such a relief not having to sleep on the floor when I arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>