<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steps on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steps on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gathering</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/gathering/</guid>
      <description>Hemmlis finds all our furniture through second hand sources. Some we collect from individuals on second hand platforms online, while other furniture reaches us through partners like Emmaus Lund. For some collections we purchase specific pieces of furniture from second hand stores or flea markets.
We also receive donations from individuals, contacting us directly through our facebook page or email address. We try to collect furniture in the immediate area around Lund, to decrease environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 10:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/fixing/</guid>
      <description>Our first task is always to sanitize incoming furniture with industry proven cleaning methods such as vacuuming, soap washing and steam washing, using environmental friendly products. This is particularly essential for textile furniture, mattresses and beds which we also treat with eco friendly methods. Subsequently we repair and upcycle the furniture when needed, by eg. repainting or repolishing.
Occasionally we reconstruct furniture or change specific parts completely to add function or aesthetically pleasing pieces to our furniture collections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The collections</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:28:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/order/</guid>
      <description>Our collections consist of 5-6 different pieces of furniture, meshed together to create a uniform design concept. We invite our guest designers to the workshop to create exciting eclectic (mixed) design concepts ranging from vintage to modern or even nordic design and rokoko. Our collections are custom made for a student room of about 15-20 square meters and always rented as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your order</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/delivery/</guid>
      <description>The minimum lease term is one semester (about five months) to a cost of 499:- a month.
All furniture will be delivered to your home address, and we will provide repairs if the need should arise, as well as pickup of the collection at the end of the term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The circle is complete</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/exchange/</guid>
      <description>Furniture that have been rented will be reintroduced into our circular system where it’s sanitized anew, and refeshed in order to be rented again. This way we create an alternative model for furniture consumtion which we believe will reduce the wastage of furniture and the following negative impact it has on the environment.
To succeed in this, it is crucial for us that our furniture be used responsibly. We put all out faith in that you, our custimers help us out in this so that we can continue to offer you neat collections of furniture in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rekate</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 11:29:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/steps/retake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>