<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lease your furniture on Hemmlis</title>
    <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lease your furniture on Hemmlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I exchange a piece of furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-substitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-substitution/</guid>
      <description>We offer the collections as they are. If you would like to replace a piece of furniture you can contact us and we can check if we have something available. We can not guarantee the possibility of replacing furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are the furniture delivered?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-delivery/</guid>
      <description>We deliver to your doorstep at a time that we both agree to. Help carrying it into your apartment is available for small one time fee. Your furniture pickup is included in the subscription! Our goal is to deliver the furniture the same day that you get access to your room. However, if there are many who are wishing to have their furniture delivered the same day, delays might incur!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I pay?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-payment/</guid>
      <description>Invoices are sent out monthly to your e-mail address and on the invoices all information you need to pay are written. If you should wish we can make one large invoice at the start of the semester so that you only need to do one payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long is the lease period?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-length/</guid>
      <description>The minimum lease period we have is at least one semester (5 months). From a semester perspective, this would be until the middle/end of June (depending on program etc.) Our other subscription is for 10 months but is therefore abit cheaper! When you wish to return your furniture you can contact us and we will book a date for a pick up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens if something breaks?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-breakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-breakage/</guid>
      <description>If a piece of furniture breaks we come out and repair/replace it. If the damage is due to normal usage (i.e &amp;ldquo;wear-and-tear&amp;rdquo;) this will not cost you anything. See your lease contract for further details about this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when my lease is up?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-ending/</guid>
      <description>We collect the furniture at the end of the lease period at a date agreed between us and you. We carry the furniture from your apartment without further costs, provided we have access to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is included?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-included/</guid>
      <description>Included in the price for both subscriptions are a collection of the following furniture types:
 One 90 cm wide bed with a fitted bed mattress One bookshelf Two wooden chairs One table (desk or small kitchen table depending on availability) One nightstand One armchair Delivery outside of your apartment (added indoor carriage service one time fee of 299:-) Pickup of furniture when you leave  You can add extra services if you wish!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who can lease the furniture?</title>
      <link>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 12:25:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hemmlis.se/en/lease/faq-who/</guid>
      <description>We are mainly targeting students with our collections which means adjusting our collections to the limited living area of 15-20 square meters. However, we want everybody to have the opportunity to try out our collections and would of course be happy to receive other requests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>